<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Genius Sports</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Genius Betting</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle"></string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="rupee"> \u20B9 </string>
    <string name="NOCONN"><![CDATA["    <string name=\"NOCONN\">Please check your internet connection.</string> "]]></string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="downloading">Downloading...</string>
    <string name="title_file_download">APK is downloading</string>
    <string name="storage_access_required">Storage access is required to downloading the file.</string>
    <string name="storage_permission_denied">Storage permission request was denied.</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <!-- Bottom Navigation -->
    <string name="pay_id">2106031403203751</string>     <!-- This is demo PAY_ID, to get your own Live PAY_ID please contact to your administrator.-->
    <string name="merchant_name">Demo</string>

    <string-array name="names">
        <item>UPI</item>
        <item>Netbanking SBI</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="hundered">100</string>
    <string name="two_hundred">200</string>
    <string name="five_hundred">500</string>
    <string name="ten_hundred">1000</string>
    <string name="add_cash_head">ADD CASH</string>
    <string name="enter_valid_amt">Enter Valid Amount</string>
    <string name="enter_min_amt">Enter minimum  Amount is 10</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="phonetxt">  </string>
    <string name="upitxt">  </string>
    <string name="banktxt"> Bank Details : STATE BANK OF INDIA HASANGANJ UNNAO UP\n NAME : ROHIT KUMAR\n ACCOUNT NO : 20104576363\n IFSC : SBIN0012863 </string>
    <string name="alert_text" />
    <string name="permission_camera_rationale11" />
    <string name="reqst_permission" />
    <string name="share_using" />
    <string name="fullScore">VIEW FULL SCORECARD</string>
    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior" translatable="false">com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
    <string name="errofirstname">please enter name</string>
    <string name="errorphonenumber">please enter mobile number</string>
    <string name="erroremailID">"please enter email "</string>
    <string name="errorPassword">please enter password</string>
    <string name="referal">please enter referal</string>
    <string name="errootp">please enter otp</string>
    <string name="howtoplayininglish">How to add money in Genius Sports app? In Genius Sports App you can PAYTM, BHIM UPI, PHONE PAY, GOOGLE PAY, NET BANKING, Through DEBIT CARD, CREDIT CARD, you can add money to the wallet of Genius Betting App. Minimum Withdraw- Minimum Withdraw limit has been kept very low in Genius Sports app. If there is only 100 rs / - in the wallet of Genius Sports app, So you can transfer these 100rs/- to your bank aacount, PHONE PAY, GOOGLE PAY, BHIM UPI, Withdraw can be done in PayTM. Withdrawal amount will be sent to your account on the same day.</string>
    <string name="howtoaddmoneyinhindi">Genius Sports app मे money Add कैसे करे ? Genius Sports App मे आप PAYTM, BHIM UPI, PHONE PAY, GOOGLE PAY, NET BANKING, DEBIT CARD, CREDIT CARD के माध्यम से Genius Betting App के wallet मे रुपये add कर सकते है . Minimum Withdraw- Genius Sports app में Minimum Withdraw की limit बहुत कम रखी गयी है. अगर Genius Sports app के wallet मे केवल 100 rs/- भी है , तो आप इन 100rs/- को अपने bank aacount, PHONE PAY , GOOGLE PAY , BHIM UPI , PAYTM में Withdraw कर सकते है. Withdraw किया हुवा Amount उसी दिन आपके account मे भेज दिया जायेगा.</string>
    <string name="howtoplayfantasyinhindi">FANTSY POINTS CONTEST मे कैसे खेलते है ? FANTSY POINTS CONTEST मे दोनो Teams से 11 Player select करके आपको एक टीम बनानी है, और किसी एक Player को Caption बनाना होगा और किसी एक Player को Vice Caption बनाना होगा. जिस Player को आप Caption बनायेंगे, उस Player द्वारा बनाये गये Point Double जायेंगे और जिस Player को आप Vice Caption बनायेंगे,उस Player द्वारा बनाये गये Point x1.5 (डेढ गुना) जायेंगे. Point Table- 1 Run- 2 points 1 Catch- 4 points 1 STAMPING- 5 POINTS 1 wicket- 6 points 1 four- 8 points 1 six- 10 points</string>
    <string name="playfantasyinenglish">HOW TO PLAY IN FANTSY POINTS CONTESTS ? In FANTSY POINTS CONTEST, you have to make a team by selecting 11 players from both the teams, and one player will have to make a Caption and one player will have to make a Vice Caption. Point made by the player to whom you will make a Caption, will be doubled and the player you will make a Vice Caption, the Point made by that player will go to x1.5 (one and a half times). Point Table- 1 Run- 2 points 1 Catch- 4 points 1 STAMPING- 5 POINTS 1 wicket- 6 points 1 four- 8 points 1 six- 10 points</string>
    <string name="howtoplaygeniusbettinginhindi">GENIUS BETTING CONTESTS मे कैसे खेलते है ? सबसे पहले आपको जिस category के contest मे खेलना है , उस पर click करे . जैसे आपको CRICKET Matches के contest मे खेलना है , तो आप cricket पर click करे. उसके बाद आप किस match मे खेलना चाहते है , उसे select करे. उसके बाद आप उस match की किस category मे खेलना चाहते है , उसे select करे. Cricket Match के UNIQUE BETTING मे कितनी sub category है इस app मे और उसमे कैसे खेलना है , उसकी जानकारी नीचे दी जा रही है. GENIUS BETTING CONTESTS Sub Category No-1---- TOSS BETTING TOSS BETTING के contest मे कौन सी टीम टॉस जीतेगी , इस तरह के Contest आयेंगे . contest मे एक तरफ एक team का नाम , Team की Entry fee , winning amount , Contest मे कितना Bonus use होगा और join button दिया होगा और दुसरी तरफ दूसरी team का नाम, दूसरी टीम की Entry fee, winning amount , contest मे कितना Bonus use होगा और join button दिया रहेगा . आपको जिस team के ऊपर contest मे पैसा लगाना हो, उस तरफ की join button पर click करके contest join कर लीजियेगा . GENIUS BETTING CONTESTS Sub Category No-2---- TEAM WIN BETTING TEAM WIN BETTING के contest मे इस मैच का नतीजा क्या होगा , इस तरह के contest होंगे. contest मे एक तरफ एक team का नाम , Team की Entry fee , winning amount , Contest मे कितना Bonus use होगा और join button दिया होगा और दुसरी तरफ दूसरी team का नाम, दूसरी टीम की Entry fee, winning amount , contest मे कितना Bonus use होगा और join button दिया रहेगा . आपको जिस team के ऊपर contest मे पैसा लगाना हो, उस तरफ की join button पर click करके contest join कर लीजियेगा . इसी तरह बहुत सी sub category Genius Betting app मे दी रहेगी . सभी Sub category मे contest का नाम हिंदी और English दोनो मे दिया रहेगा .</string>
    <string name="howplaygeniusbettinginenglish">HOW TO PLAY GENIUS BETTING CONTESTS? First of all, click on the category in which you want to play in the contest. Like you have to play in the contest of CRICKET Matches , then you click on cricket. After that select in which match you want to play. After that, in which category of the match you want to play, select it. How many sub-category are there in the UNIQUE BETTING CONTESTS of Cricket Match in this app and how to play in it, its information is being given below. GENIUS BETTING CONTESTS Sub Category No-1---- TOSS BETTING Which team will win the toss in the contest of TOSS BETTING, such contests will come. The name of a team on one side in the contest, Team\'s entry fee, winning amount, how much bonus will be used in the contest and join button will be given And on the other hand the name of the other team, entry fee of the other team, winning amount, how much bonus will be used in the contest And the join button will be given. On the team on which you want to invest money in the contest, you will join the contest by clicking on the join button on that side. GENIUS BETTING CONTESTS Sub Category No-2---- TEAM WIN BETTING What will be the result of this match in the TEAM WIN BETTING contest, there will be such a contest. one in the contest On the side the name of a team, entry fee of the team, winning amount, how much bonus will be used in the contest And the join button will be given and on the other hand the name of the other team, entry fee of the other team, winning amount, in the contest How much bonus will be used and join button will be given. The team on which you have money in the contest If you want to put it, you will join the contest by clicking on the join button on that side. Similarly, many sub-category will be given in Genius Betting app. In all sub categories, the name of the contest will be given in both Hindi and English.</string>
    <string name="playliveinhindi"><![CDATA[LIVE BETTING ( PLAY & WIN UNLIMITED MONEY ) मे कैसे खेलते है? मैच शुरु होते ही LIVE BETTING की Category आपको Genius Sports app मे दिखने लगेगी. LIVE BETTING ( PLAY & WIN UNLIMITED MONEY मे कई तरह के Contest आयेंगे , जैसे कौन सी टीम टॉस जीतेगी और कौन सी टीम मैच जीतेगी. इस तरह के Contests मे आप जितना पैसा लगाना चाहते है उतना लगा सकते है. इस तरह के Contest मे आप Live Match के दौरान भी पैसे लगा सकते है . इस तरह के Contest मे मैच के दौरान दोनो Teams का winning amount बदलता रहता है . जैसा कि दुसरे Betting app मे होता है . मान लीजिये INDIA और SRI LANKA का मैच है और INDIA के मैच जीतने के ज्यादा Chance है , तब आपने अगर INDIA पर 1000rs लगाये और INDIA जीत जाती है, तो आपको लगभग 1400rs या 1500rs मिल सकते है . वही SRI LANKA पर पैसे लगाते है और SRI LANKA जीत जाती है , तब आपको 2000 rs या 2200 rs तक आपको मिल सकते है . eniusbettinginhindi]]></string>
    <string name="playliveinenglish"><![CDATA[HOW TO PLAY IN LIVE BETTING ( PLAY & WIN UNLIMITED MONEY )? As soon as the match starts, you will start seeing the category of LIVE BETTING in Genius Sports app. There will be many types of contests in LIVE BETTING ( PLAY & WIN UNLIMITED MONEY ), like which team will win the toss and which team will win the match. You can invest as much money as you want in such contests. In this type of contest, you can also invest money during Live Match. In this type of contest, the winning amount of both the teams keeps changing during the match. As in other betting app. Suppose there is a match of INDIA and SRI LANKA and INDIA has more chances to win the match, then if you put 1000rs on INDIA and INDIA wins, then you can get around 1400rs or 1500rs. The same SRI invests money on LANKA and SRI LANKA wins, then you can get 2000 rs or up to 2200 rs.]]></string>
    <string name="playuniqinhindi">UNIQUE BETTING CONTEST मे कैसे खेले ? UNIQUE BETTING CONTEST मे मैच से सम्बंधित कुछ प्रश्न दिये रहते है. जैसे कौन सी टीम टॉस जीतेगी , कौन सी टीम मैच जीतेगी, कौन सी टीम ज्यादा बाउंड्री मारेगी, कौन सी टीम ज्यादा विकेट लेगी, 5 overs तक किस टीम के ज्यादा रन होंगे, 10 overs तक किस टीम के ज्यादा रन होंगे, 15 overs तक किस टीम के ज्यादा रन होंगे, इस तरह के बहुत से प्रश्न Contest मे दिये रहेंगे. मैच खत्म होने के बाद आपके द्वारा दिये गये प्रश्नो के उत्तर सही होते है तो प्रत्येक सही उत्तर के लिये आपको 10 points मिलेंगे और जिस user के सबसे ज्यादा points होंगे उसको rank के हिसाब से winning amount मिलेगा. UNIQUE BETTING CONTEST मे आप 25रु की entry fee pay करके लाखो कमा सकते है.</string>
    <string name="hedingrefferal">You can win money without playing a contest in Genius Sports and even if you lose a contest in Genius Sports, you can still win Rs. If the user in GENIUS SPORTS registers another user in GENIUS SPORTS through his Refer code, then the user gets extra income, which is not available in any other Fantasy or Betting app. In Genius Sports app you do not play as a user but you join Genius Sports as a partner because in Genius Sports app you can win lakhs of rupees by playing yourself but also by connecting other users with your Refer code. You can earn money without playing. Category wise information about how other users will get extra income by linking them with their refer code is being given below.</string>
    <string name="livebettingtext">If any user added by your refer code joins the contest in any match of the category of LIVE BETTING, then you will get 5% percent of the user\'s entry fee. Suppose the user added by you has put 1000rs/- on a team in any match of this category, then you will get 5% percent of 1000rs/- i.e. Rs 50. If the team on which the user you have added, loses the team, still you will get 5% percenrt of the entry fee i.e. if the other user\'s team loses or wins, you will get 5% percent of the entry fee every time. Similarly, if 10 people added by your refer code play in the category of LIVE BETTING with an entry fee of Rs 1000 then the total entry fee will be 10000/- (ten thousand rupees) and you will get 10000/- (ten thousand rupees) 5% of percent i.e. Rs.500/- will be available as commission. That is, in Genius Sports, you can win lakhs by playing yourself and you can earn lakhs in the form of commission by connecting other users with your refer code. G</string>
    <string name="uniqueheading">2- UNIQUE BETTING CONTESTS , GENIUS BETTING CONTESTS, FANTSY POINTS CONTESTS-</string>
    <string name="uniquetext">In the contests of these three categories of Genius Sports, you get referral commission in two ways. If any user added by your refer code joins the contest of these three categories then you will get 5% percent commission of entry fee as well as 3% percent extra commission of any contest the user added by you will win Rs. will get. Suppose the user added by you has joined the contest by depositing an entry fee of Rs 1000 in a contest and that user wins Rs 20000 in that contest, then 3% percent of the Rs 20000 won by the user in that contest, you will get Rs 600 as commission. And even if the user loses that contest, you will still get a commission of 5% percent 50 of the entry fee of Rs 1000.</string>
    <string name="headinhhindi">Genius Sports मे बिना Contest खेले आप रुपये जीत सकते है और यदि आप Genius Sports मे कोई Contest हारते भी है तब भी आप रुपये जीत सकते है . यदि GENIUS SPORTS मे user अपने Refer code के माध्यम से किसी दुसरे user का GENIUS SPORTS मे रजिस्ट्रेशन करवाता है, तो User को extra income होती है, जो किसी दुसरे Fantasy या Betting app मे नही मिलती है. Genius Sports app मे आप एक User की तरह नही खेलते है बल्कि Genius Sports को आप एक पार्टनर की तरह Join करते है क्योकि Genius Sports app मे आप खुद तो खेल कर लाखो रुपये जीत ही सकते है बल्कि दुसरे users को अपने Refer code से जोङकर भी बिना खेले ही पैसे कमा सकते है. दुसरे users को अपने Refer code से जोङकर extra income कैसे होगी, इसकी जानकारी Category के हिसाब से नीचे दी जा रही है-</string>
    <string name="livetexthindi">यदि आपके refer code द्वारा जोङा गया कोई भी user LIVE BETTING की Category के किसी भी मैच मे Contest join करता है, तो user की entry fee का 5% percent आपको मिलेगा. मान लीजिये आपके द्वारा जोङे गये user ने इस Category के किसी मैच मे 1000rs/- किसी Team पर लगाये तो आपको 1000rs/- रुपये का 5% percent यानी 50रु आपको मिलेंगे. अगर आपके द्वारा जोङे गये user ने जिस Team पर पैसा लगाया है वो Team हार भी जाती हें फिर भी आपको entry fee का 5% percenrt आपको मिलेगा यानि दुसरे user की Team हारें या फिर जीते आपको हर बार entry fee का 5% percent मिलेगा. इसी तरह अगर आपके refer code द्वारा जोङे गये 10 लोग LIVE BETTING की Category मे 1000रु की entry fee के साथ खेलेते है तो कुल entry fee 10000/- (दस हजार रुपये ) होगी और आपको 10000/- (दस हजार रुपये ) के 5% percent यानी 500रु/- कमीशन के रुप मे मिलेंगे. यानी Genius Sports मे आप खुद खेलकर भी लाखो जीत सकते है और दुसरे Users को अपने refer code से जोङकर भी कमीशन के रूप मे लाखो कमा सकते है.</string>
    <string name="uniquetexthindi">Genius Sports की इन तीन Category के contests मे आपको दो तरह से referral commission मिलता है. यदि आपके refer code द्वारा जोङा गया कोई भी user इन तीन Category के contest को join करता है तो entry fee का 5% percent कमीशन मिलेगा और साथ ही साथ आपके द्वारा जोङा गया user जिस भी contest मे रुपये जीतेगा उसका 3% percent extra कमीशन आपको मिलेगा. मान लीजिये आपके द्वारा जोङे गये user ने किसी contest मे 1000रु की entry fee जमा करके contest join किया और वो user उस contest मे 20000रु जीतता है , तो user द्वारा उस contest मे जीते गये 20000रु का 3% percent 600रु आपको कमीशन के रूप मे मिलेंगे और यदि user उस contest को हार भी जाता है, तब भी आपको entry fee 1000रु का 5% percent 50रु आपको commission मिलेगा.</string>
    <string name="howtoplayenglishunique">HOW TO PLAY IN UNIQUE BETTING CONTEST? In UNIQUE BETTING CONTEST some questions related to the match are given. Like which team will win the toss, which team will win the match, which team will hit more boundaries, which team will take more wickets, which team will have more runs up to 5 overs, which team will have more runs up to 10 overs, up to 15 overs Which team will have more runs, many such questions will be given in the contest. After the match is over, the answers given by you are correct, then for each correct answer you will get 10 points and the user who has the most points will get the winning amount according to the rank. In UNIQUE BETTING CONTEST, you can earn lakhs by paying an entry fee of Rs.25.</string>
    <string name="errorPasswords">password not match</string>
    <string name="rgisterrefertext">यदि आपके पास कोई भी Refer code नहीं है, तो आप यह Refer code डालकर अपना Registration कर‌ सकते हैं. If you do not have any Refer code, then you can register yourself by entering this Refer code .</string>
    <string name="addmoneyinhindi">GENIUS SPORTS के ‍WALLET में रुपये कैसे ADD करें ? VIDEO देखने के लिये Watch Video in Hindi या Watch Video in English पर Click करें .:</string>

</resources>
